Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part I WAG.025.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Supplement
  - Subseries V:C: Addendum
    - Union for the Defense of the Human Person, 1947 (Box 53B, Folder 27)
    - Unions-ILGWU, 1944-1945 (Box 53B, Folder 28)
    - United Hebrew Trades, 1945 (Box 53B, Folder 29)
    - Vladeck Funeral, 1938 (Box 53B, Folder 30)
    - Warsaw Ghetto Commemoration, 1947 (Box 53B, Folder 31)
    - Workmen's Circle, 1934 (Box 53B, Folder 32)
    - Workmen's Circle, Jan 1943-Feb 1943 (Box 53B, Folder 33)
    - Workmen's Circle, Mar 1943-Apr 1943 (Box 53B, Folder 34)
    - Workmen's Circle, May 1943-Jun 1943 (Box 53B, Folder 35)
      Reel#: 168
    - Workmen's Circle, Jul 1943-Sep 1943 (Box 53B, Folder 36)
    - Workmen's Circle, Oct 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 53B, Folder 37)
    - Workmen's Circle, 1944 (Box 53B, Folder 38)
    - Index Card File: Delegate Cards, Jewish Labor Committee Founding Convention, Feb 25, 1934 (Box 53B, Folder data_value_missing_98d0101ec4d2813d9fab1750e64f2516)